[{"answer": "I do.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 11, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 10}, {"answer": "Tonight he's back talking candidly and emotionally about Farrah, Tatum and his other children, and his own battle with cancer.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 14, "question": "Piers Morgan, are you?", "qSentId": 13}, {"answer": "I feel that I failed Farrah.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 28, "question": "Did you conclude that?", "qSentId": 27}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know if I'm qualified to judge politics, but I think there is a kind of convergence here.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "Is that a fair allegation, do you think?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "Well, it certainly was not covert.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 49, "question": "From what you saw and witnessed ground, what would you say?", "qSentId": 48}, {"answer": "Well, you know, it depends on what we feel is a failure.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "And in a sense, if they don't, then the original point of this war, to go in, yes, to take on al Qaeda but also to take on the Taliban, who are protecting the al Qaeda operatives, if that fails, if the Taliban simply revert to the way they were before, and there is a genuine fear they do that, then the overall gambit, if you like, of the war would have failed, won't it?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "Freaky, yes.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 104, "question": "So in the first instance I was really shocked and I said, oh my god, what is it?", "qSentId": 103}, {"answer": "I went to see him first.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "And who went to see who first?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "In Chicago.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "In Chicago?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "He cooked me Indonesian food on that day.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "What did he cook you?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": "It was really good, it was really good.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "Any good?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "Yes, I did.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 132, "question": "Did you feel a brother-sister thing?", "qSentId": 131}, {"answer": "It was a moment of great pride because, you know, I was so proud of him.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "What did you feel?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "Definitely, definitely.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 193, "question": "Did you approve of your brother's choice of bride?", "qSentId": 192}, {"answer": "I said well done, little brother, well done.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "Do you remember what you said to him?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "No, no, because he's always my brother and he remains my brother.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "Not much more to say, really, is there?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "As much as you speak to your sibling, your brother or your sister, depending on what your work, you know, your time allows.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "Can you speak to him if he's president much?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "Is it that easy?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "Look, you can call the White House, there's a number.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "What, he picks the phone up?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "Yes, I --", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 232, "question": "You must have been there a few times, right?", "qSentId": 231}, {"answer": "You know, the thing is, he has such a particular job to do, and I do a certain kind of job myself.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "Do you sometimes say to him, look, mate, you're my brother and here's my advice on this?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "She's a mother of four children.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "What does your sister do, what is her job?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "I did, I heard it.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "Did you hear that?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "I heard it the first time when he did it on TV.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "At Christmas parties, does he do the Al Green impression?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "No, my brother has a sense of humor.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "Did you know he had a good voice?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "Thank you.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "It's an amazing story, isn't it?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "Yes, there is a Web site.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "What is it?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "Fine.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "Quite good, actually.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "How are things now?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "I don't think it was very helpful, no.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "ORGAN: Was that helpful or not, doing that show?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "Well, they said you're against him, remember that.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "In what way?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "Well, we thought we had a plan, she and I, in that we would make stuff up.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 362, "question": "You think from the start the premise was never going to work for you two?", "qSentId": 361}, {"answer": "Well, I don't plan to give in to it.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "So what is the prognosis for you?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "Yes, this is your life generally.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "'NEAL: To the story?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "He's -- he hasn't read it.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "How's he doing?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "You have no contact with him?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "Well, I know I tried.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "Do you feel, when you read the book back and you read all this stuff and relived it all -- do you feel you gave parenting your best shot or do you think that you were too selfish, perhaps, at times?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "I don't know about that.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 438, "question": "Did you try hard enough?", "qSentId": 437}, {"answer": "I feel that I failed Farrah.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "Did you conclude that?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "Do you regret that now?", "qSentId": 482}, {"answer": "Only her.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "But do you think you're capable of ever loving like that again?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "Well, I missed her inappropriately.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "Did you ever hit her inappropriately, now that you look back at it?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "I -- she went into a bathroom and I punched the door and the door collapsed and hit her in the eye and I broke my hand.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "Did you ever try and punch her?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "He was -- he was exposed to two people who loved each other very much, and was confused by what was happening now.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "-- a pretty chaotic world, wasn't he?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "I think she's saying a -- a smart thing, absolutely.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "What do you think of what she says there?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "What -- I don't know what you mean.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "I mean when you -- when you said, oh, what's the other one called, how did you feel after you -- you said that?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "Well, I thought I was writing about Farrah, but -- but they were around.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 585, "question": "I mean you've written a book about them, so I guess it's fair to ask, isn't it?", "qSentId": 584}, {"answer": "No, do you think you fuel -- continue to fuel the circus, when, if you write a book about all the trials and tribulations --", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 592, "question": "I fueled the circus?", "qSentId": 591}, {"answer": "No, I -- I don't.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 609, "question": "You don't feel you have to go down and get a license?", "qSentId": 608}, {"answer": "As well as I can.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 621, "question": "How do you deal with that?", "qSentId": 620}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 635, "question": "I mean, do you think you ever will be able to?", "qSentId": 634}, {"answer": "No, or either the home or the memory of Farrah --", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 637, "question": "Let go of my home?", "qSentId": 636}, {"answer": "It's the kind of scene that is in films.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 654, "question": "In that moment, how did you feel, when she realized what you were doing?", "qSentId": 653}, {"answer": "Well, my thoughts were for Redmond, because he was in jail and he didn't know.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 671, "question": "The moment you knew you'd lost her, that she'd gone, obviously, you were grief-stricken, but what did you think would happen to the rest of your life without Farrah anymore, given how young she was, comparatively?", "qSentId": 670}, {"answer": "He likes me.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 683, "question": "What does he make of you as a dad, do you think, now?", "qSentId": 682}, {"answer": "I -- I don't think about it.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 694, "question": "I mean in an ideal world, how would you see it mapping out?", "qSentId": 693}, {"answer": "No --", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 697, "question": "Do you see making movies as part of that?", "qSentId": 696}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "120502pmt", "aSentId": 699, "question": "Would you like to?", "qSentId": 698}]